SIMON VERHEYEN

PROFILE

My foundation in physics has given me a strong basis in advanced mathematics and a good statistical understanding.

Through my work in DHL I have learned how to work and communicate as part as a team, how to delegate and problem solve to overcome unexpected issues and secure the workflow, as well as to communicate across departments, with management or third parties to achieve productive cooperation.

With my last role as data manager I rediscovered my love for data analysis and programming. So, when I went to finish my bachelor, I took machine learning and as many computer sciences courses I could. Combined with online specialization courses in deep learning optimization and advanced python use I want to dive into my passion for a project I can believe in.

CONTACT

Phone:

+32.484 / 21 34 31

Email:

siverheyen@gmail.com

Portfolio:

http://github.com/simonverheyen/Portfolio

EDUCATION

Free University Brussels

2008 - 2014, 2018 - 2019 Bachelor Physics & Astronomy Minor in computer science

WORK EXPERIENCE

DHL 3PL - Data Management

02/2018 - 08/2018 (Prague & Brussels)

Solely responsible for storage and correct processing of the global DHL stock exchange for a client, HP, through warehouse and transport tags. Requiring weekly, monthly and yearly reporting as well as implementation of new requests, or resolving of conflicts within the databases and reports.

DHL ITS - Team leader

02/2018 - 04/2018 (Prague)

Interim team leader, which was shared with one other colleague, for the BNL, De and 3PL team. Which was a total of 14 people. This consisted of managing the 3 teams schedules, complications and requests as well as communication with management, high level support, local IT and team up-scaling.

DHL ITS - Service Desk Specialist

02/2017 - 02/2018 (Prague)

Assisting the team leader for BNL, De and 3PL with inter department communications, improvement of workflow and management and training of the teams. Combined with being the main knowledge base and communication point for the, internationally specialized, third party logistics support.

DHL ITS - Service Desk Analyst

04/2016 - 02/2017 (Prague)

Contact point for IT support for DHL employees within Benelux. Assisting with account management and first analysis of IT issues with troubleshooting, where the access allowed it.

Later joining a three-man team on top of the BNL support, for specialized support for global users third party logistics users.

Famifed: Federal Agency for Child Support - Administrative Assistant

04/2015 – 10/2015 (Brussels)

Management and analysis of large-scale data of family composition and child support. Assisting with the compilation of a yearly report and research into areas of improvement for, or issues in, the support system.

LANGUAGES:

Dutch Native

English Fluent

French Intermediate

German Basic understanding

KEY SKILLS

Advanced mathematics

Statistics **Physics**

Team support & management Third party communication

Microsoft office

Microsoft troubleshooting

Data base management Deep learning optimization

Machine learning

PROGRAMMING:

PROFESIONAL CERTIFICATIONS

HDI Certified: Desktop Support Technician

Certified Logistics Professional

ITILV1 Certified

Coursera – Python for everybody

Deeplearning.ai – Deep Learning Optimization specialization:

Course 1, 2, 3

Driving license B

C#

С

Python

C++

Scala

Linux

SQL

Basics

MS Acc.

Intermediate

Advanced

Basics

Basics

Intermediate

Intermediate

Intermediate

Github

Intermediate